Guide to the Doris Ulmann Photograph Collection ca. 1910-1934 PR 72
New-York Historical Society
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158076 (Item 1142)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158075 (Item 1143)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158074 (Item 1144)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158073 (Item 1145)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158072 (Item 1146)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158071 (Item 1147)
- medium gray jacket, vest, patterned tie, dark graying hair, dark eyebrows [Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, "Harper's Bazaar," c. 1925], 158070 (Item 1148)
- white hair, mustache, dark eyebrows, jacket, patterned tie [Shaw, Albert, editor, "Everybody's" magazine, c. 1925], 158069 (Item 1149)
  #1149, 1167, 1168, 2931 is same subject, this is another image of subject in "A Portrait Gallery of American Editors"
- jacket, tie, pince nez eyeglasses, smooth hair [Squier, J. Bentley, Professor of Urology, Columbia], 1919; 158068 (Item 1150)
  #1150, 1205, 1263, 1361, 1372 same subject, this is another image of subject in "XXIV Portraits"
- dark jacket, vest, striped tie, watch chain [Lamb, Charles Rollinson (1860-1942)], 1916; 158067 (Item 1151)
- dark hair, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, standing very upright gripping arm of chair, 158066 (Item 1152)
- man seated at desk, young man showing him letters or papers, 1917; 158065 (Item 1153)
- seated, jacket, bow tie, gray (or blond) hair, holding cigarette and box of matches, 158064 (Item 1154)
- balding, gray hair, mustache, jacket, tie, vest [Butler, Nicholas Murray, President Columbia], 1918; 158063 (Item 1155)
  #1155, 1270, 1324, 2408, 2409, 3009 same subject, another image of subject in "XXIV Portraits"
- gray suit, tie, white hair, mustache, beard, 1916; 158062 (Item 1156)
- dark double breasted jacket, vest, tie, dark hair [Heyward, Dubose, southern writer], 158061 (Item 1157)
  #1157, 1366, 2895 same subject; wrote Porgy and Bess libretto
- seated on sofa, two framed paper pieces on wall above him, coat, jacket, vest, tie, watch chain, hat on sofa next to him, 158060 (Item 1158)
- standing, coat, tie, vest, white hair, beard, mustache, 1916; 158059 (Item 1159)
  #1159, 1455 same subject
- seated at desk with paper, dark jacket, vest, tie, balding, mustache [Elliot, John Lovejoy], 1917; 158058 (Item 1160)
  identified on mat
- two men in suits playing checkers, 1918; 158057 (Item 1161)
- shirtsleeves, tie, apron, seated by a photographic enlarger or copy camera [Huntington, George S., Professor of Anatomy, Columbia], 1918; 158056 (Item 1162)
  #1162, 1163, 1312, 1314, 2967 same subject; another image of subject in "XXIV Portraits"
- white hair, mustache, beard, in dark gown [Huntington, George S., Professor of Anatomy, Columbia], 1918; 158055 (Item 1163)
  #1162, 1163, 1312, 1314, 2967 same subject; another image of subject in "XXIVe Portraits"
- dark jacket, tie, dark hair, balding with book, 158054 (Item 1164)
  1162, 1163, 1312, same subject; another image of subject in "XXIV Portraits"
- striped suit, patterned shirt and tie, gray hair, mustache, beard, round eyeglasses, with open book, 158053 (Item 1165)
- dark smooth hair, dark jacket, vest, one hand on hip, 158052 (Item 1166)
- dark suit, tie white hair [Albert Shaw, editor, "Everybody's" magazine, c. 1925], 158051 (Item 1167)
  #1149, 1167, 1168, 2931 is same subject
- dark suit, tie white hair, smiling [Albert Shaw, editor, "Everybody's" magazine, c. 1925], 158050 (Item 1168)
- dark double breasted jacket, vest, medium dark balding hair and mustache [Maclean, Charles Thomas Agnew, editor, "Popular Magazine"], 158049 (Item 1169)
  #1169, 2328, 2654, 3008 same subject; another image of subject in "A Portrait Gallery of American Editors"
- at easel with paint brush, artists smock, tie, shirt with white collar [Weber, Max], 158048 (Item 1170)
- two men in work clothes seated in front of a large sculpture of a woman holding her very large breasts, 158047 (Item 1171)
  #1171, 1172, same subject
- two men in work clothes seated in front of a large sculpture of a woman holding her very large breasts, 158046 (Item 1172)
- dark suit, white hair [Van Vechten, Carl (1880-1964) writer, photographer], 158045 (Item 1173)
- dark hair, long, smoothed back, mustache, dark jacket, vest, tie, 158044 (Item 1174)
- in shirtsleeves, dark tie, with cigarette, 158043 (Item 1175)
- in cardigan sweater, bow tie, with cane, newspaper, seated, gray hair, mustache, beard, 158042 (Item 1176)
- wavy light colored hair, jacket, vest, striped tie, 158041 (Item 1177)
- older man, cap, white hair, mustache, bushy eyebrows [Hoag, Mr.], 158040 (Item 1178)
  in Ulmann's handwriting on back of mat: Portrait Mr. Hoag, Doris Ulmann, 1000 Park Avenue, New York City; also is rubber stamped: Pittsburgh Salon of Photography 1925; #1178, 1349 same subject
- dark hair, straight, light colored jacket, vest, patterned tie, 158039 (Item 1179)
- dark hair, suit, tie, vest, with cigarette, 158038 (Item 1180)
- white hair, dark suit, tie, 158037 (Item 1181)
- dark mustache, heavy dark hair, almost smiling [Mumford, Lewis, American writer and critic], 158036 (Item 1182)
  #1182, 2168, 2235 same subject
- short gray hair, with photograph (?) [Frost, Robert], 158035 (Item 1183)
  #1183, 1249, 1250, 1519, 1525, 2050, 2293 same subject
- young, medium dark curly hair, suit, tie, holding burning cigarette, 158034 (Item 1184)
  #1184, 1283, 1285 same subject
- light hair, stocky, smiling, suit, tie [Lorimer, George Horace, editor in chief, Saturday Evening Post], 158033 (Item 1185)
  #1185, 2805, 2936 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery", not this image
- longish white/gray hair, bushy mustache, suit, tie, vest, seated [Garland, Hamlin (1860-1940) writer], 158032 (Item 1186)
  #1186 - 1188 same subject, ID per Leslie Chapman notes 1999
- longish white/gray hair, bushy mustache, suit, tie, vest, seated [Garland, Hamlin (1860-1940) writer], 158031 (Item 1187)
- longish white/gray hair, bushy mustache, suit, tie, vest, seated with book, second man had long darker hair, round eyeglasses, mustache, suit, tie, vest [Garland, Hamlin (1860-1940) writer], 158030 (Item 1188)
- white hair, mustache, beard, round eyeglasses, suit, tie, vest, 158029 (Item 1189)
  #1189, 1190 same subject
- white hair, mustache, beard, round eyeglasses, suit, tie, vest, 1918; 158028 (Item 1190)
- felt hat, overalls, work shirt, 158027 (Item 1191)
- hat, work shirt, overalls, handlebar mustache, 158026 (Item 1192)
  #1192, 1194 same subject
- middle aged, wide brimmed straw hat, graying beard and mustache, black shirt, white suspenders, smiling, 158025 (Item 1193)
- hat, work shirt, overalls, handlebar mustache, 158024 (Item 1194)
- medium dark hair, long white beard, mustache, work shirt, suspenders, 158023 (Item 1195)
  #1195-1198 same subject
- straw hat, medium dark hair, long white beard, mustache, work shirt, suspenders, 158022 (Item 1196)
- straw hat, medium dark hair, long white beard, mustache, work shirt, suspenders, 158021 (Item 1197)
- straw hat, medium dark hair, long white beard, mustache, work shirt, suspenders, 158020 (Item 1198)
- felt hat, white hair, beard, mustache, jacket, overalls, 158019 (Item 1199)
- polka dot work shirt, suspenders, round glasses, light colored hair, balding, 158018 (Item 1200)
- bushy white mustache, light colored felt hat, pipe, reading newspaper, 158017 (Item 1201)
- thick dark hair, curly, suit, tie, vest [Nathan, George Jean, editor, The American Mercury], 158016 (Item 1202)
  #1202, 2979 same subject
- balding, patterned bow tie, jacket, vest [Whiggham, Henry James, editor, Town and Country], 158015 (Item 1203)
  #816, 1203, 1228, 3013 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery", but not this image
- dark suit, vest, bow tie, white hair, balding [Galsworthy, John (1867-1933) English writer], 158014 (Item 1204)
- smooth medium gray hair, pince nez eyeglasses, suit, tie [Squier, J. Bentley, Professor of Urology, Columbia], 1919; 158013 (Item 1205)
- young, dark smooth hair, parted in middle, jacket, tie, vest, holding cigarette [Wescott, Glenway (writer)], 158012 (Item 1206)
  #1206, 2299 same subject; per Leslie Chapman notes 1999; another image in Bookman Dec. 1929
- pinstriped suit, white hair, mustache, beard, sideburns, 1918; 158011 (Item 1207)
- gray suit, vest, tie, white hair [Bennett, John], 158010 (Item 1208)
  noted on mat and in Xerox binder: other copies in Charleston; copies rcvd Oct. 1989 from Grandson, John Bennett Jr., Attorney at Law, 16 Fulton St., P. O. Box 127, Charleston, South Carolina 29402, see Paladines correspondence Dec. 1989
- older, balding, white beard and mustache [Bradford, Gamaliel (1863-1932) American Biographer], 158009 (Item 1209)
- white hair, beard, sideburns, mustache, oval eyeglasses, writing at desk with papers, books, suit, tie, 158008 (Item 1210)
- medium dark smooth hair, jacket, vest, tie, 158007 (Item 1211)
- thick graying hair, round eyeglasses, suit, vest, striped tie, holding cigarette, 158006 (Item 1212)
  #1212, 1248 same subject
- smooth dark hair, suit, tie, with violin, 158005 (Item 1213)
  #1213, 1214 same subject
- smooth dark hair, suit, tie, writing at desk, 158004 (Item 1214)
- striped blouse or smock, curly dark hair, at easel, 158003 (Item 1215)
  #1215, 1704 same subject
- in long jacket, with palette, brush, white hair, beard, mustache, at easel painting a landscape [Dow, Arthur Wesley, artist and theorist (1857-1922)], 1919; 158002 (Item 1216)
  #1216, 1238, 1239, 2712 same subject; identification per Lesley Chapman notes 1999: most likely Arthur Wesley Dow
- medium dark bushy hair, beard, mustache, in smock in studio [Robinson, Boardman, American painter], 158001 (Item 1217)
- medium dark bushy hair, beard, mustache, in smock in studio [Robinson, Boardman, American painter], 158000 (Item 1218)
- sailor, on dock, in harbor, smoking cigarette, 157999 (Item 1219)
- in smock, almost smiling [Weber, Max], 157998 (Item 1220)
  #966, 1170, 1220, 202, 2555 same subject, Ulmann's Art and Design teacher at Clarence H. White School of Photography
- in white doctor's scrubs, round eyeglasses, bald, 1919; 157997 (Item 1221)
  #1221, 1222, 1411 same subject; NOT in Columbia "XXIV Portraits.. ."
- in dark doctor's scrubs, round eyeglasses, bald, 1919; 157996 (Item 1222)
- gray hair, patterned shirt, very thin necktie [Blue, Chief Samuel], 157995 (Item 1223)
  # 1132, 1223, identified on 1223 mat in Ulmann's handwriting
- white hair, round eyeglasses, gray suit, vest, tie, almost smiling, with musical score, 157994 (Item 1224)
- medium dark hair, mustache, beard, suit, tie, 157993 (Item 1225)
  #1225, 1226 same subject
- medium dark hair, mustache, beard, suit, tie, smiling, 157992 (Item 1226)
- dark hair, balding, mustache, round glasses, at desk, suit, tie, 157991 (Item 1227)
- balding, patterned bow tie, suit, vest [Whigham, Henry James, editor, Town and Country], 157990 (Item 1228)
  #816, 1203, 1228, 3013same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery", but not this image
- with pipe, manuscript or magazine [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157989 (Item 1229)
  #1229-1231, 2143-2152, 2724, 2984 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. ." but not this image
- with pipe, writing at desk [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157988 (Item 1230)
- with pipe, with manuscript [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157987 (Item 1231)
- young man, light hair, balding, with small notepad, 157986 (Item 1232)
- gray hair, in velvet and satin smoking jacket, writing, 157985 (Item 1233)
- round eyeglasses, gray hair and mustache, suit, tie, vest with book, 157984 (Item 1234)
- young, light thick curly hair, white short sleeved shirt [Green, Paul Eliot (1894-1981), writer, dramatist], 157983 (Item 1235)
  #1235, 2002-2004, 2199, 2201, 2227-2231, 2243 same subject, mat is missing
- straight white hair, parted in middle, suit, tie, vest, 157982 (Item 1236)
- dark hair, balding, suit, vest, tie, with pipe, 157981 (Item 1237)
  #1237, 2269, 2335 same subject
- white hair, mustache, beard, seated with books [Dow, Arthur Wesley, artist and theorist (1857-1922)], 1919; 157980 (Item 1238)
- white hair, mustache, beard, seated with books [Dow, Arthur Wesley, artist and theorist (1857-1922)], 1919; 157979 (Item 1239)
- military uniform, seated, medium dark hair, mustache, 1919; 157978 (Item 1240)
- top hat, white tie [Niles, John Jacob, (1892-1980) folklorist, musician, Ulmann's assistant], 157977 (Item 1241)
  #1241, 1242, 2722, 2723 same subject
- at piano [Niles, John Jacob, (1892-1980) folklorist, musician, Ulmann's assistant], 157976 (Item 1242)
- medium dark hair, parted in middle, round eyeglasses, suit, vest, tie, 157975 (Item 1243)
- light colored hair, suit, vest, tie, 157974 (Item 1244)
  #1244, 1246 same subject
- balding, smooth hair, dark mustache, thin face, dark suit, tie, 157973 (Item 1245)
- light colored hair, suit, vest, tie, at desk with papers, 157972 (Item 1246)
- balding, medium dark hair, suit, tie, with book [Page, Arthur Wilson, editor, World's Work], 157971 (Item 1247)
  #1247, 2930, 3006 same subject; subject in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image
- thick graying hair, round eyeglasses, suit, vest, striped tie, holding cigarette, 157970 (Item 1248)
- dark suit [Frost, Robert], 157969 (Item 1249)
- dark suit [Frost, Robert], 157968 (Item 1250)
- polka dot bow tie, light gray suit, light colored hair, with cigarette, 157967 (Item 1251)
- tweed suit, vest tie, medium dark hair, 1919; 157966 (Item 1252)
- thin face, dark hair, parted in middle, with cigarette, 157965 (Item 1253)
- curly dark hair, dark mustache, suit, vest, tie, 157964 (Item 1254)
- seated at desk [Tilney, Frederic, Professor of Neurology and Neuro-Anatomy, Columbia], 157963 (Item 1255)
- thin face, thinning dark hair, seated with cigarette [Wilder, Thornton], 157962 (Item 1256)
  #1017, 1081, 1256, 1605 same subject
- dark straight hair, distinguished long nose, tweed jacket, seated with pipe at desk, 157961 (Item 1257)
- missing from box, 157960 (Item 1258)
- dark smooth hair, parted on side, striped shirt, collar bar, tie, dark suit, vest, 157959 (Item 1259)
- dark, thick, curly hair, with cigarette [Wolfe, Thomas, writer], 157958 (Item 1260)
  #1260, 1467, 1490 same subject
- dark hair, suit, tie, vest, seated, watch, 157957 (Item 1261)
- dark, thick curly hair, dark suit, tie, vest, seated with book, 157956 (Item 1262)
- smooth medium gray hair, pince nez eyeglasses, suit, tie [Squier, J. Bentley, Professor of Urology, Columbia], 1919; 157955 (Item 1263)
  #1150, 1205, 1263, 1361, 1372 same subject
- graying hair, dark bushy eyebrows, smiling, suit, tie, 157954 (Item 1264)
  #1264, 1265 same subject
- profile, with cigarette, 157953 (Item 1265)
- pince nez eyeglasses, balding, suit, tie, vest, watch chain, 157952 (Item 1266)
- balding, mustache, with book [Adler, Felix, philosopher and founder of Ethical Culture Society], 1916; 157951 (Item 1267)
- felt hat, seated at organ, 157950 (Item 1268)
- graying dark hair, mustache, beard, stiff white collar and white tie, suit, vest, 157949 (Item 1269)
- jacket, tie, pince nez eyeglasses, smooth hair [Butler, Nicholas Murray, President Columbia], 1918; 157948 (Item 1270)
  #1155, 1270, 1324, 2408, 2409, 3009 same subject
- work shirt, guitar, 157947 (Item 1271)
  According to David Featherstone, this is a performer at Bunyan's Pilgrim's Progress Day in Ashland, KY, c. 1933
- Asian Indian or Pakistani, dark suit, tie, vest, reading book [Battaghanjee], 157946 (Item 1272)
  # 2899-2904 same subject, per Leslie Chapman notes 1999: Identified as Battaghanjee (we're not sure who exactly he was)
- gray hair, cleft chin, suit, tie, vest, 1919; 157945 (Item 1273)
- jowls, bow tie, bushy eyebrows [Cobb, Irvin S.], 157944 (Item 1274)
- pince nez eyeglasses, bow tie [Long, Ray, editor, The Cosmopolitan], 157943 (Item 1275)
  #1275, 2804 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image
- young, short curly blonde hair, white shirtsleeves, with pipe, 157942 (Item 1276)
  #1276, 1699, 1700, 1703 same subject
- suit, tie, vest, boutonniere [Johnson, James Weldon poet, diplomat, songwriter, and anthologist of black culture], 157941 (Item 1277)
- striped shirt, bow tie, white hair, bushy eyebrows, 1918; 157940 (Item 1278)
- striped shirt, bow tie, white hair, bushy eyebrows, pince nez eyeglasses, with newspaper, 1918; 157939 (Item 1279)
- jacket, sweater vest, tie, round eyeglasses, white or gray hair, 157938 (Item 1280)
- dark thinning hair, jacket, tie, with open book, 157937 (Item 1281)
- thick, dark hair, curly, dark round eyeglasses, suit, vest, tie, 157936 (Item 1282)
- young, dark thick curly hair, tie loosened, open collar, 157935 (Item 1283)
- white or gray hair, suit, tie, 157934 (Item 1284)
- young, dark curly hair, suit, vest, tie, 157933 (Item 1285)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157932 (Item 1286)
  #1073, 1286-1288, 2125-2134, 2999 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery of Am. Ed.", but not this image
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, with book of garden illustrations [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157931 (Item 1287)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, with book, at desk [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157930 (Item 1288)
- dark, smooth hair, with cigarette, suit, vest, tie, 157929 (Item 1289)
  1289-1290 same subject
- dark, smooth hair, with cigarette, suit, vest, tie, 157928 (Item 1290)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, black armband on left arm, slouched on window seat [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157927 (Item 1291)
  1291-1306, 1515 same subject
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, slouched on window seat [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157926 (Item 1292)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, at desk [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157925 (Item 1293)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157924 (Item 1294)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, with book [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157923 (Item 1295)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie,, laying on couch with pillows, head propped on his hand [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157922 (Item 1296)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, black armband on left arm, smiling, with cigarette [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157921 (Item 1297)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, black armband on left arm [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157920 (Item 1298)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, seated with book [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157919 (Item 1299)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, black armband on left arm, seated [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157918 (Item 1300)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, seated, writing [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157917 (Item 1301)
- mustache, suit, vest, tie, seated, with cigarette [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157916 (Item 1302)
- in riding habit, jodhpurs, cap, crop, gloves, almost smiling [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157915 (Item 1303)
- in riding habit, jodhpurs, cap, crop, gloves, standing, smiling [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157914 (Item 1304)
- in riding habit, jodhpurs, cap, crop, gloves, standing, smiling [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157913 (Item 1305)
- in riding habit, jodhpurs, cap, crop, gloves, standing, smiling, teeth [Boyd, James (1888-1944), writer], 157912 (Item 1306)
- thin, smooth medium dark hair, smooth fair skin [Finemen, Irving, writer, (close friend of Ulmann and Julia Peterkin)], 157911 (Item 1307)
  #1307, 1730 same subject; see index under Irving Finemen, "The Life and Photography.. .", Jacobs for passages from letters, description of relationship
- white hair, beard, double breasted suit, 157910 (Item 1308)
  1308-1311 same subject
- white hair, beard, double breasted suit, 157909 (Item 1309)
- white hair, beard, double breasted suit, 157908 (Item 1310)
- white hair, beard, double breasted suit, 157907 (Item 1311)
- lab smock, at workbench with microscope [Huntington, George S., Professor of Anatomy, Columbia], 157906 (Item 1312)
  #1162, 1163, 1312, 1314, 2967 same subject
- missing from box, 157905 (Item 1313)
- in lab smock [Huntington, George S., Professor of Anatomy, Columbia], 157904 (Item 1314)
- white/white hair, parted in middle, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, 1919; 157903 (Item 1315)
- white hair, mustache, jacket, tie, vest, 157902 (Item 1316)
- in military uniform, white hair, mustache, 1919; 157901 (Item 1317)
- medium dark thinning hair, suit, vest, tie, seated, 157900 (Item 1318)
- medium dark thinning hair, dark eyebrows, suit, vest, tie, seated, 157899 (Item 1319)
- dark straight thinning hair, suit, vest, tie [Untermeyer, Louis, American poet (1885-1977)], 157898 (Item 1320)
- striped shirt and suit, vest, tie, pince nez eyeglasses, thinning medium dark hair, mustache, 157897 (Item 1321)
- thin white hair, mustache, beard, suit, vest, tie, 157896 (Item 1322)
- balding, gray hair, mustache, with pipe, suit, tie, vest, 157895 (Item 1323)
- balding, graying hair, mustache [Butler, Nicholas Murray, President Columbia], 1918; 157894 (Item 1324)
- white hair, sideburns, mustache, bushy eyebrows, seated, typing on typewriter [Smith, Stephen], 157893 (Item 1325)
  per Leslie Chapman notes, 1999: Identified at UK [Univ. of Kentucky?] as Dr. Stephen Smith
- white mustache, military uniform, decorations, 157892 (Item 1326)
  #1326, 1444, 1888, 1889, 1914-1918, 2100-2108 same subject
- profile, gray hair, with cigarette, dark suit, tie, 157891 (Item 1327)
  #1327, 2192, 2215 same subject
- young, wavy dark hair, striped suit, tie, with cigarette, 157890 (Item 1328)
- striped shirt, with papers [Galsworthy, John (1867-1933) English writer], 157889 (Item 1329)
  #969, 978, 1074, 1204, 1329-1330, 1424, 1454, 1500-1502, 1715, 2338, 2758 same subject; this image appears in Bookman December 1929
- polka dot bow tie [Galsworthy, John (1867-1933) English writer], 157888 (Item 1330)
- young, very dark hair and eyebrows, pencil mustache, suit, tie, vest, dark round eyeglasses [La Farge, Oliver], 157887 (Item 1331)
  #1331, 2308 same subject
- thin gray hair, round eyeglasses, suit, tie, 157886 (Item 1332)
- dark, thin hair, smooth complexion, suit, tie, vest, holding pipe, oval eyeglasses, 157885 (Item 1333)
- young, dark curly hair, suit, tie, vest, 157884 (Item 1334)
- white hair, suit, tie, vest, with letter, 157883 (Item 1335)
- balding, with pince nez eyeglasses, smiling [Walpole, Sir Hugh], 157882 (Item 1336)
  identified by Leslie Chapman, notes 1999
- white hair, handlebar mustache, suit, tie, 157881 (Item 1337)
- dark curly hair, mustache, suit, tie, vest, 157880 (Item 1338)
- white mustache, suit, black bow tie [Weir, Robert F., Professor of Surgery, Columbia], 1918; 157879 (Item 1339)
- gray hair, mustache, linen suit, 157878 (Item 1340)
  #1340, 1341 same subject
- gray hair, mustache, linen suit, 157877 (Item 1341)
- jacket, work shirt, white beard and mustache, with newspaper, 157876 (Item 1342)
- cap, jacket, work shirt, white hair, mustache, 157875 (Item 1343)
  #1343, 1345 same subject
- cap, round eyeglasses, work shirt, apron, suspenders, blacksmith (?), 157874 (Item 1344)
- cap, jacket, work shirt, white hair, mustache, 157873 (Item 1345)
- fisherman in boat in river with net, 157872 (Item 1346)